<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.fda.gov/">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA Food Safety Recalls RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://www.fda.gov/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Kayco Issues an Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Limited Units of Glicks Dark  Chocolate Conettos</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kayco-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-limited-units-glicks-dark-chocolate-conettos</link>
  <description>Kayco, a Bayonne NJ company is recalling their Glicks Dark Chocolate Conettos because it may contain undeclared milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk, run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products. </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:52:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kayco-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-limited-units-glicks-dark-chocolate-conettos</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Kedake Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Sesame, Soy, Wheat, Yellow No. 5, Yellow No. 6, and Red No. 6 in Botana Mix Snacks</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kedake-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-sesame-soy-wheat-yellow-no-5-yellow-no-6-and-red-no-6</link>
  <description>KEDAKE, INC. of Houston, TX is recalling it’s 2 lb packages of Las Ollas Botana Mix Snacks because they may contain undeclared Sesame, Soy, Wheat, Yellow No 5, Yellow No 6, and Red No 6. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to Sesame, Soy, Wheat, Yellow No 5, Yellow No 6 and Red No 6, ru</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:19:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kedake-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-sesame-soy-wheat-yellow-no-5-yellow-no-6-and-red-no-6</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>ZB Importing Issue Voluntary Recall and Allergy Alert on Undeclared Egg, Wheat and Milk in Certain Ulker Brand Products</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/zb-importing-issue-voluntary-recall-and-allergy-alert-undeclared-egg-wheat-and-milk-certain-ulker</link>
  <description>ZB Importing LLC is voluntarily recalling certain lots of six varieties of Ulker Brand snack rolls, biscuits, and wafers due to undeclared wheat, egg and/or milk in the Ingredient List and/or Contains Statement on the product labels. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to wheat, egg, or</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 13:12:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/zb-importing-issue-voluntary-recall-and-allergy-alert-undeclared-egg-wheat-and-milk-certain-ulker</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Naturipe Value Added Fresh LLC Issues Allergy Alert On Undeclared Wheat &amp; Eggs In "Berry Buddies, Berries &amp; Pancakes” Lot # 1097901</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/naturipe-value-added-fresh-llc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-wheat-eggs-berry-buddies-berries</link>
  <description>Naturipe Value Added Fresh LLC. of Alma, GA, is recalling its 2.1 oz./60 gram packages of "Berry Buddies, Berries &amp;amp; Pancakes" bento box snack packs because they contain wheat and EGGS that were not declared on the label. People who have allergies to WHEAT and/or EGGS run the risk of serious allergic</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 08:35:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/naturipe-value-added-fresh-llc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-wheat-eggs-berry-buddies-berries</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Mauna Loa Macadamia Nut Company, LLC Issues a Product Recall on Undeclared Almonds in Mauna Loa Milk Chocolate Covered Macadamias (1oz) Pouches</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/mauna-loa-macadamia-nut-company-llc-issues-product-recall-undeclared-almonds-mauna-loa-milk</link>
  <description>Mauna Loa Macadamia Nut Company LLC of Kea’au, HI is voluntarily recalling one batch of its Mauna Loa Milk Chocolate Covered Macadamias snack (1oz) pouches, due to the presence of undeclared almonds which are an allergen. </description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/mauna-loa-macadamia-nut-company-llc-issues-product-recall-undeclared-almonds-mauna-loa-milk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>JE Bakery 2019 LLC DBA Broadway Bakery Issues Allergy Alert for Mislabeled Raisin Bran Muffin 6 Count Due to Undeclared Walnuts</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/je-bakery-2019-llc-dba-broadway-bakery-issues-allergy-alert-mislabeled-raisin-bran-muffin-6-count</link>
  <description>JE Bakery 2019, LLC, Minneapolis MN is voluntarily recalling its Raisin Bran Muffin 6 count due to a labeling error. The affected product was mislabeled and instead contains Glorious Morning Muffins, which contains Walnuts, a known allergen not declared on the label.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 10:05:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/je-bakery-2019-llc-dba-broadway-bakery-issues-allergy-alert-mislabeled-raisin-bran-muffin-6-count</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>AKT Trading Inc. Recalls Seasoned Bamboo Shoots Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/akt-trading-inc-recalls-seasoned-bamboo-shoots-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>AKT Trading Inc of Torrance, California is recalling 120 packages of Menma Ajitsuke Prepared Bamboo Shoot Product, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Clostridium botulinum, a bacterium which can cause life-threatening illness or death.  Consumers are warned not to use the product e</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:56:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/akt-trading-inc-recalls-seasoned-bamboo-shoots-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Jack and the Green Sprouts Recalls Expired Alfalfa Sprouts Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jack-and-green-sprouts-recalls-expired-alfalfa-sprouts-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Jack and the Green Sprouts, Inc. of River Falls, WI is recalling 5oz packages of Alfalfa sprouts that expired on 1/29/25 because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elde</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:53:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jack-and-green-sprouts-recalls-expired-alfalfa-sprouts-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Tri-Union Seafoods Issues Recall of Select Genova®, Van Camp’s®, H-E-B and Trader Joe’s® Tuna Cans Due to Clostridium Botulinum Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/tri-union-seafoods-issues-recall-select-genovar-van-campsr-h-e-b-and-trader-joesr-tuna-cans-due</link>
  <description>Tri-Union Seafoods has made the decision to voluntarily recall select lots of canned tuna products sold under the Genova®, Van Camp’s®, H-E-B and Trader Joe’s brand names.  This voluntary recall is out of an abundance of caution following the notification from our supplier that the “easy open” pull </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:02:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/tri-union-seafoods-issues-recall-select-genovar-van-campsr-h-e-b-and-trader-joesr-tuna-cans-due</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Turkana Food Inc. Recalls Aleppo Tahini Sesame Paste 1lb (16oz) Because of Possible Health Risk </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/turkana-food-inc-recalls-aleppo-tahini-sesame-paste-1lb-16oz-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Turkana Food Inc. Kenilworth, NJ is recalling 858 cases OF Aleppo Tahini Sesame Paste because it has the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune system</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 12:43:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/turkana-food-inc-recalls-aleppo-tahini-sesame-paste-1lb-16oz-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Gerber Products Company Announces Recall and Discontinuation of All Batches of   Gerber® Soothe N Chew® Teething Sticks Due To Choking Hazard</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/gerber-products-company-announces-recall-and-discontinuation-all-batches-gerberr-soothe-n-chewr</link>
  <description>January 31, 2025 — Gerber Products Company is initiating a recall and discontinuation of all batches of GERBER® SOOTHE N CHEW® TEETHING STICKS due to a potential choking hazard for babies and young children</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 18:54:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/gerber-products-company-announces-recall-and-discontinuation-all-batches-gerberr-soothe-n-chewr</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Blue Ridge Beef Issues a Recall of Blue Ridge Beef Natural Mix Due to Salmonella Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/blue-ridge-beef-issues-recall-blue-ridge-beef-natural-mix-due-salmonella-contamination</link>
  <description>January 31, 2025– Blue Ridge Beef is recalling 5,700 lbs. of their 2 lb log Natural Mix due to a contamination of Salmonella. Lot # N25/12/31 (Lot numbers are stamped in the clips on the end of the chubs/bags) UPC# 854298001054.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 14:38:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/blue-ridge-beef-issues-recall-blue-ridge-beef-natural-mix-due-salmonella-contamination</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>United Natural Trading LLC Announces Allergy Alert for Undeclared Milk in Fresh Direct Dark Chocolate Covered Pretzels</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/united-natural-trading-llc-announces-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-fresh-direct-dark-chocolate</link>
  <description>January 29, 2025 – United Natural Trading LLC, Edison, NJ, is voluntarily recalling Fresh Direct Dark Chocolate Covered Pretzels due to the presence of an undeclared milk allergen.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:31:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/united-natural-trading-llc-announces-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-fresh-direct-dark-chocolate</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Wismettac Asian Foods Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Curvee Puffs Corn Puff Snack</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/wismettac-asian-foods-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-curvee-puffs-corn-puff-snack</link>
  <description>Wismettac Asian Foods, Inc., Santa Fe Springs, CA is expanding its January 17, 2025 recall of 2.46 oz packages of Shirakiku brand Curvee Puffs Corn Puff Snack Curry Flavor. The expansion now includes two additional flavors; Sea Salt &amp;amp; Umami Flavor and Corn Potage Flavor. The product contains the und</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 20:08:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/wismettac-asian-foods-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-curvee-puffs-corn-puff-snack</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>New York Wholesale Group Recalls Zaarah Herbals Shatavari Powder Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-york-wholesale-group-recalls-zaarah-herbals-shatavari-powder-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>New York Wholesale Group of Hicksville, NY is recalling Zaarah Herbals Shatavari Powder, to the consumer/user level because it has the potential to be contaminated with elevated levels of lead. Short term exposures to very low levels of lead may not elicit any symptoms.  It is possible that increase</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:26:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-york-wholesale-group-recalls-zaarah-herbals-shatavari-powder-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Recall of La Fiesta Brand Bread Crumbs (Unseasoned and Seasoned) for Undeclared Sesame</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/recall-la-fiesta-brand-bread-crumbs-unseasoned-and-seasoned-undeclared-sesame</link>
  <description>La Fiesta Food Products, LLC, La Mirada, CA is recalling 8 oz packages of La Fiesta brand Unseasoned Bread Crumbs (Pan Rayado) and Seasoned Bread Crumbs (Pan Rayado Sazonado). The products contain sesame as an undeclared allergen. Additionally, the labels do not include the allergen declaration in S</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:27:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/recall-la-fiesta-brand-bread-crumbs-unseasoned-and-seasoned-undeclared-sesame</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>TS Food Packaging is Recalling its “Rural King” and “Wabash Valley Farms” Bacon Seasoning Due to the Presence of an Undeclared Soy Ingredient</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ts-food-packaging-recalling-its-rural-king-and-wabash-valley-farms-bacon-seasoning-due-presence</link>
  <description>TS Food Packaging is recalling its “Rural King” and “Wabash Valley Farms” Bacon Seasoning due to the presence of an undeclared soy ingredient. People who have allergies to products containing soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reactions if they consume these products.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:03:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ts-food-packaging-recalling-its-rural-king-and-wabash-valley-farms-bacon-seasoning-due-presence</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>D. Coluccio &amp; Sons, Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Almonds in “Colussi Cantuccini Chocolate Drops” Cookies</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/d-coluccio-sons-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-almonds-colussi-cantuccini-chocolate-drops-cookies</link>
  <description>D. COLUCCIO &amp;amp; SONS, in is recalling its 300 gram packages of “Colussi Cantuccini Chocolate Drops” chocolate chip cookies because they may contain undeclared almonds.  </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/d-coluccio-sons-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-almonds-colussi-cantuccini-chocolate-drops-cookies</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Monkey Spit, LLC Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk/Wheat/Soy in  Monkey Spit BBQ Sauces</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/monkey-spit-llc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milkwheatsoy-monkey-spit-bbq-sauces</link>
  <description>People who have allergies to milk/wheat/soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products. The three recalled “Monkey Spit BBQ Sauces" were distributed locally in retail stores on the central coast of California and through mail orders on our website:</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 21:35:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/monkey-spit-llc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milkwheatsoy-monkey-spit-bbq-sauces</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Wismettac Asian Foods Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Curvee Puffs Corn Puff Snack Curry Flavor</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/wismettac-asian-foods-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-curvee-puffs-corn-puff-snack-curry-flavor</link>
  <description>Wismettac Asian Foods, Inc., Santa Fe Springs, CA is recalling 2.46 oz packages of Shirakiku brand Curvee Puffs Corn Puff Snack Curry Flavor. The product contains the undeclared milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reacti</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:43:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/wismettac-asian-foods-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-curvee-puffs-corn-puff-snack-curry-flavor</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
