<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.fda.gov/">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA Food Safety Recalls RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://www.fda.gov/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Homegrown Family Foods Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Shore Lunch Oven Style Breader &amp; Batter Mix</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/homegrown-family-foods-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-shore-lunch-oven-style-breader-batter</link>
  <description>Homegrown Family Foods is recalling its Shore Lunch Oven Style Breader &amp;amp; Batter Mix 6oz Box due to the presence of undeclared milk. Individuals with an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk risk serious or life-threatening allergic reactions if they consume this product. For ease of identification, </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/homegrown-family-foods-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-shore-lunch-oven-style-breader-batter</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Isabelle’s Kitchen Inc. Recalls Refrigerated Deli Salads Containing Fresh Cucumbers Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/isabelles-kitchen-inc-recalls-refrigerated-deli-salads-containing-fresh-cucumbers-because-possible</link>
  <description>Isabelle's Kitchen, Inc., Harleysville, PA, is recalling 946 cases of refrigerated deli salads containing fresh cucumbers recalled by Bedner Grower’s, Inc. because they have potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young chil</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:07:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/isabelles-kitchen-inc-recalls-refrigerated-deli-salads-containing-fresh-cucumbers-because-possible</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Supreme Service Solutions LLC Voluntarily Recalls Supreme Vegetable Products Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/supreme-service-solutions-llc-voluntarily-recalls-supreme-vegetable-products-because-possible-health-0</link>
  <description>Supreme Service Solutions LLC. (dba Supreme Produce) is voluntarily recalling items purchased from Bedner Growers Inc. (purchased from Kroger and its affiliates ) due to possible contamination with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frai</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 16:22:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/supreme-service-solutions-llc-voluntarily-recalls-supreme-vegetable-products-because-possible-health-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Santa Monica Seafood Voluntarily Recalls Atlantic Salmon Portions with Seafood Stuffing Due to Undeclared Soy </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/santa-monica-seafood-voluntarily-recalls-atlantic-salmon-portions-seafood-stuffing-due-undeclared</link>
  <description>May 24, 2025, Santa Monica Seafood of Rancho Dominguez, CA, is voluntarily recalling Atlantic Salmon Portions with Seafood Stuffing because it may contain undeclared soy. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to soy risk a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 16:56:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/santa-monica-seafood-voluntarily-recalls-atlantic-salmon-portions-seafood-stuffing-due-undeclared</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Spectrum Brands Pet LLC Recalls a Single Lot of Tetra Reptomin Reptile Food for Aquatic Turtles Because of Possible Salmonella Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/spectrum-brands-pet-llc-recalls-single-lot-tetra-reptomin-reptile-food-aquatic-turtles-because</link>
  <description>Spectrum Brands Pet LLC (“SPG”) is voluntarily recalling its Tetra ReptoMin 3-In-1 SELECT-A-FOOD reptile food product intended for aquatic turtles due to potential contamination with Salmonella. The product is packaged in a plastic, 1.56oz container with a green label and a UPC Bar Code #: 0 46798 7</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:01:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/spectrum-brands-pet-llc-recalls-single-lot-tetra-reptomin-reptile-food-aquatic-turtles-because</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>JFE Franchising, Inc. Recalls A Limited Number of Cucumber Products   Because Of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jfe-franchising-inc-recalls-limited-number-cucumber-products-because-possible-health-risk-0</link>
  <description>Houston, TX (May 23, 2025) - JFE Franchising, Inc. of Houston, TX, is recalling a limited number of fresh-cut cucumber items and sushi products containing cucumber because they may be contaminated with Salmonella.  </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:40:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jfe-franchising-inc-recalls-limited-number-cucumber-products-because-possible-health-risk-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Big Y Foods Recalls Made-To-Order Subs, Wraps and Paninis Sold in Massachusetts and Connecticut Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/big-y-foods-recalls-made-order-subs-wraps-and-paninis-sold-massachusetts-and-connecticut-because</link>
  <description>Big Y Foods of Springfield, MA is voluntarily recalling some Made-To-Order Subs, Wraps and Paninis sold between 5/20 and 5/21 in some Massachusetts and Connecticut retail stores (listed below), because they have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious a</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:10:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/big-y-foods-recalls-made-order-subs-wraps-and-paninis-sold-massachusetts-and-connecticut-because</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Albertsons Companies Voluntarily Recalls Three Store-Made Deli Items  Containing Recalled Cucumber Supplied by Fresh Creative Foods Due to Possible Salmonella Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-three-store-made-deli-items-containing-recalled-cucumber</link>
  <description>Following a recall initiated by Fresh Creative Foods, a division of Reser’s Fine Foods, Inc., Albertsons Companies has voluntarily recalled three store-made deli items, supplied by Fresh Creative Foods, due to possible Salmonella contamination and in association with an active illness outbreak. The </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:05:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-three-store-made-deli-items-containing-recalled-cucumber</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>The Coastal Companies Issues Voluntary Recall on Items with Fresh Start Cucumbers Due to the Potential for Salmonella Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/coastal-companies-issues-voluntary-recall-items-fresh-start-cucumbers-due-potential-salmonella</link>
  <description>The Coastal Companies is issuing a voluntary recall of 17 products that were produced from cucumbers grown by Bedner Growers, Inc. and distributed by Fresh Start Produce Sales, Inc. due to the potential for Salmonella contamination. These products were distributed by East Coast Fresh in Laurel, MD a</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:18:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/coastal-companies-issues-voluntary-recall-items-fresh-start-cucumbers-due-potential-salmonella</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Walmart Inc. Recalls Marketside Fresh Cut Cucumber Slices in Select Texas Stores Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/walmart-inc-recalls-marketside-fresh-cut-cucumber-slices-select-texas-stores-because-possible-health</link>
  <description>BENTONVILLE, Ark. May 22nd, 2025 Walmart Inc. is voluntarily recalling Marketside Fresh Cut Cucumber Slices, produced in select stores located in Texas, because of the potential for Salmonella contamination. The recall was initiated because this product may contain recalled whole cucumbers supplie</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/walmart-inc-recalls-marketside-fresh-cut-cucumber-slices-select-texas-stores-because-possible-health</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Ukrop’s Homestyle Foods Announces Recall Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ukrops-homestyle-foods-announces-recall-due-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Ukrop’s Homestyle Foods, LLC, Richmond, VA announced today that it is recalling three of its products in reaction to the Bedner Growers’ recall of cucumbers due to its potential to be contaminated with Salmonella.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:26:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ukrops-homestyle-foods-announces-recall-due-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>PennRose Farms Issues Recall of Whole Cucumbers  Because Of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/pennrose-farms-issues-recall-whole-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Wellington, FL (May 21, 2025)—PennRose Farms, LLC is recalling 5-pound mesh bags of whole cucumbers because they have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weake</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:55:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/pennrose-farms-issues-recall-whole-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>New Grains Gluten Free Bakery Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Eggs, Tree Nuts, Soy, and Milk in Bakery Products</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-grains-gluten-free-bakery-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-eggs-tree-nuts-soy-and-milk-bakery</link>
  <description>May 21, 2025 — Spanish Fork, Utah — New Grains Gluten Free Bakery is recalling a variety of products, including breads, bagels, cookies, and croutons, because they may contain undeclared eggs, tree nuts, soy, and milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs, tree nuts, soy, or milk</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:12:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-grains-gluten-free-bakery-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-eggs-tree-nuts-soy-and-milk-bakery</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Bedner Growers, Inc. Recalls Cucumbers Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/bedner-growers-inc-recalls-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Bedner Growers, Inc. of Boynton Beach, Florida is voluntarily recalling cucumbers sold at Bedner’s Farm Fresh Market between April 29, 2025, and May 14, 2025 because they have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in youn</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 12:10:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/bedner-growers-inc-recalls-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>R&amp;M Trading LLC Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in R&amp;M Refresher Instant Milk Tea Powder</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/rm-trading-llc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-rm-refresher-instant-milk-tea-powder</link>
  <description>R&amp;amp;M Trading LLC of Lakewood, WA is recalling approximately 408 packages (1lb. pack per package) and 1624 packages (3/1lb. packs per package) of Instant Milk Tea powder products because they may contain undeclared milk. </description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/rm-trading-llc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-rm-refresher-instant-milk-tea-powder</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>South Asian Food Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Peanuts in "Bengal King Family Pack Vegetable Singara"</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/south-asian-food-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-peanuts-bengal-king-family-pack-vegetable</link>
  <description>South Asian Food Inc. of Maspeth, NY, is recalling its 1875g packages of Bengal King Family Pack Vegetable Singara because they may contain undeclared peanuts. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to peanuts run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume th</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:24:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/south-asian-food-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-peanuts-bengal-king-family-pack-vegetable</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Element 112, LLC dba Madeline’s Pâtisserie Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Wheat in Croissants and Croissant Buns</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/element-112-llc-dba-madelines-patisserie-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-wheat-croissants-and</link>
  <description>Sylvania, Ohio (May 15, 2025) Element 112, LLC dba Madeline’s Pâtisserie is issuing a voluntary recall of a specific batch of our ready-to-eat croissants, due to a labeling error. The ingredient statement on the exterior of the box was labeled as “flour” and does not accurately reflect the contained</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/element-112-llc-dba-madelines-patisserie-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-wheat-croissants-and</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>NatureMills US Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Wheat, Milk, and Sesame in Rice Mixes, Soups, Spice Mixes, Porridge Mix, Papads and Vadam Products</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/naturemills-us-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-wheat-milk-and-sesame-rice-mixes-soups-spice</link>
  <description>NatureMills US Inc., based in Prosper, Texas, is recalling select products that were sold between December 1, 2023, and May 10, 2025, due to undeclared allergens: Wheat, Milk, and Sesame. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to these allergens run the risk of serious or life-threatening </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:50:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/naturemills-us-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-wheat-milk-and-sesame-rice-mixes-soups-spice</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Ariana Sweets Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Sesame and Wheat in AFGHANI CORN BREAD (“Doda”)</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ariana-sweets-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-sesame-and-wheat-afghani-corn-bread-doda</link>
  <description>May, 13, 2025, Ariana Sweets Inc. of Fremont, CA is recalling AFGHANI CORN BREAD “Doda” manufactured prior to 4/24/2025, because it may contain undeclared sesame and wheat.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to sesame or wheat run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic react</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:22:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ariana-sweets-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-sesame-and-wheat-afghani-corn-bread-doda</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Knockro Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Almonds in Bonya Yogurt Parfaits</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/knockro-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-almonds-bonya-yogurt-parfaits</link>
  <description>Knockro Inc., PA, is recalling its Bonya-branded yogurt parfait products due to an undeclared almond. Specifically, the granola component in some of these products contains almonds, which were not listed on the label. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to almonds risk serious or life-t</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:11:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/knockro-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-almonds-bonya-yogurt-parfaits</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
