<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.fda.gov/">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA Food Safety Recalls RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://www.fda.gov/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Palermo Villa, Inc. Issues Recall for 1,728 Connie’s Thin Crust Cheese Frozen Pizzas Due to Possible Plastic Contaminant</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/palermo-villa-inc-issues-recall-1728-connies-thin-crust-cheese-frozen-pizzas-due-possible-plastic</link>
  <description>December 13, 2024 Palermo Villa, Inc. is issuing a recall of 1,728 Connie’s Thin Crust Cheese Frozen Pizzas because of a possible plastic foreign contaminant. The product was distributed in Illinois, Minnesota, and Wisconsin to retail grocery stores. The affected product, Connie’s Thin Crust Cheese </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 18:57:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/palermo-villa-inc-issues-recall-1728-connies-thin-crust-cheese-frozen-pizzas-due-possible-plastic</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Motivate Me Ashley, LLC is Recalling VidaSlim Brand 90-Day, 30-day and 7-Day Original  Root, Root Plus, and Root Capsules &amp; VidaSlim Hot Body Brew Due to the Presence of Yellow  Oleander in the Products</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/motivate-me-ashley-llc-recalling-vidaslim-brand-90-day-30-day-and-7-day-original-root-root-plus-and</link>
  <description>Motivate Me Ashley, LLC of San Antonio, Texas is recalling the following VidaSlim brand products: VidaSlim 90-day (Original Root, Root Plus, and Root Capsules), VidaSlim 30-day (Original Root, Root Plus, and Root Capsules), VidaSlim 7-day Sample Size (Original Root, Root Plus, and Root Capsules), an</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 16:21:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/motivate-me-ashley-llc-recalling-vidaslim-brand-90-day-30-day-and-7-day-original-root-root-plus-and</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>New Age International Recalls ‘Enoki Mushrooms’ Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-age-international-recalls-enoki-mushrooms-due-potential-health-risk</link>
  <description>New Age International Inc of Brooklyn, NY 11206 is recalling its 200g packaged of Daily Veggies Enoki Mushroom, Product to Korea because they maybe contaminated with Listeria Monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 17:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-age-international-recalls-enoki-mushrooms-due-potential-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Riverside Natural Foods Inc. Issues Voluntary Recall of Select  MadeGood Granola Bar Products Over Potential Presence of a Piece of Metal</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/riverside-natural-foods-inc-issues-voluntary-recall-select-madegood-granola-bar-products-over</link>
  <description>Riverside Natural Foods Inc. is voluntarily recalling certain batches of MadeGood granola bars due to the potential presence of a piece of metal in the product, which, if consumed, may result in a safety hazard. The health and safety of our consumers is our highest priority. This recall is being ini</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:14:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/riverside-natural-foods-inc-issues-voluntary-recall-select-madegood-granola-bar-products-over</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Borsari Food Co. Recalls – Bloody Mary Mix – Due to Possible Health Risk </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/borsari-food-co-recalls-bloody-mary-mix-due-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Borsari Food Co of Jamestown, NY is recalling all of its Bloody Mary Mix due to undeclared allergens. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to fish (anchovy), or soy that are not declared on the label run the risk of a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these pr</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:29:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/borsari-food-co-recalls-bloody-mary-mix-due-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Reser’s Fine Foods, Inc. Recalls Select Lots of Sprouts Farmers Market Gyro Family Kits Due to Potential Salmonella Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/resers-fine-foods-inc-recalls-select-lots-sprouts-farmers-market-gyro-family-kits-due-potential</link>
  <description>Select lots of Gyro Family Kits were recalled from Sprouts stores on 12/06/2024 after being alerted by their supplier Reser’s Fine Foods, Inc. of potential Salmonella contamination of the cucumbers within the tzatziki sauce. No illnesses have been reported to date.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 08:58:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/resers-fine-foods-inc-recalls-select-lots-sprouts-farmers-market-gyro-family-kits-due-potential</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Voluntary Product Recall Notification – Gyro Sandwich Express Meal Kit Due to Cucumber Ingredient Linked to Baloian Farms Recall</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/voluntary-product-recall-notification-gyro-sandwich-express-meal-kit-due-cucumber-ingredient-linked</link>
  <description>Baloian Farms of Arizona Co. (Baloian) has initiated a recall of cucumbers due to possible health risks due to salmonella.  As a result, Fresh Creative Foods is voluntarily recalling one product that contains cucumbers in the tzatziki sauce included in the kit. </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/voluntary-product-recall-notification-gyro-sandwich-express-meal-kit-due-cucumber-ingredient-linked</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>F&amp;S Fresh Foods Recalls Mediterranean Inspired Party Tray Because of Possible Health Risk Due to Potential Salmonella Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/fs-fresh-foods-recalls-mediterranean-inspired-party-tray-because-possible-health-risk-due-potential</link>
  <description>F&amp;amp;S Fresh Foods, Riverside, CA is recalling Mediterranean Inspired Party Tray 22 oz. The recall was initiated after F&amp;amp;SFresh Foods was notified that Grecian Delight Tzatziki sauce supplied to F&amp;amp;S Fresh Foods may be contaminated with&lt;br&gt;
Salmonella because it contains cucumbers recalled by Sunfed Produce </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/fs-fresh-foods-recalls-mediterranean-inspired-party-tray-because-possible-health-risk-due-potential</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Atkinson Milling Company Recalls Frozen 1 Lb Bag Frozen Hushpuppies with Onions, 2 Lb 8oz Bag Frozen Hushpuppies With Onions and 2 Lb 8oz Bag Frozen Hushpuppies Without Onions Due to Undeclared Milk </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/atkinson-milling-company-recalls-frozen-1-lb-bag-frozen-hushpuppies-onions-2-lb-8oz-bag-frozen</link>
  <description>Atkinson Milling Company is recalling a variety of Hushpuppies due to undeclared milk allergen (products are listed below).  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products. </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:04:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/atkinson-milling-company-recalls-frozen-1-lb-bag-frozen-hushpuppies-onions-2-lb-8oz-bag-frozen</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Hardie’s Fresh Foods Recalls Cucumbers Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/hardies-fresh-foods-recalls-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Dairyland Produce, LLC, dba Hardie’s Fresh Foods of Houston, TX and Dallas, TX are recalling CUCUMBER SELECT 6 CT, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella,</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/hardies-fresh-foods-recalls-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>JFE Franchising, Inc. Recalls A Limited Number of Cucumber Products  Because Of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jfe-franchising-inc-recalls-limited-number-cucumber-products-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>JFE Franchising, Inc. of Houston, TX, is recalling a limited number of products because they may be contaminated with Salmonella. </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 16:24:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jfe-franchising-inc-recalls-limited-number-cucumber-products-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Yummi Sushi LLC Voluntarily Recalls Cucumber Products Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/yummi-sushi-llc-voluntarily-recalls-cucumber-products-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Potential to be contaminated with Salmonella. Yummi Sushi LLC. of Farmers Branch, TX  is assisting in a voluntary Kroger Store recall for cucumbers purchased from Sunfed Produce LLC Recall (purchased from Kroger Stores) due to possible contamination with Salmonella. Salmonella is an organism that ca</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 01:47:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/yummi-sushi-llc-voluntarily-recalls-cucumber-products-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Supreme Service Solutions LLC Voluntarily Recalls Supreme Produce Cucumber Products Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/supreme-service-solutions-llc-voluntarily-recalls-supreme-produce-cucumber-products-because-possible</link>
  <description>Potential to be contaminated with Salmonella. .Supreme Service Solutions LLC. (dba Supreme Produce) of Farmers Branch, TX is assisting in a voluntary Kroger Store recall for cucumbers purchased from Sunfed Produce LLC Recall (purchased from Kroger Stores) due to possible contamination with Salmonell</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:45:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/supreme-service-solutions-llc-voluntarily-recalls-supreme-produce-cucumber-products-because-possible</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Walmart Inc. Recalls Marketside Fresh Cut Cucumber Slices in 34 Texas Stores Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/walmart-inc-recalls-marketside-fresh-cut-cucumber-slices-34-texas-stores-because-possible-health</link>
  <description>Following a recall initiated by SunFed Produce, LLC, Walmart Inc. has voluntarily recalled Marketside Fresh Cut Cucumber Slices, produced in select stores, due to the potential for Salmonella contamination. The recall was initiated because this product may contain recalled whole cucumbers supplied b</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 11:55:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/walmart-inc-recalls-marketside-fresh-cut-cucumber-slices-34-texas-stores-because-possible-health</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Baker Farms Recalls Baker Brand Curly Mustard Due to Listeria Monocytogenes Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/baker-farms-recalls-baker-brand-curly-mustard-due-listeria-monocytogenes-contamination</link>
  <description>Baker Farms is recalling their Baker Farms Curly Mustard, 16 oz. plastic bags with BEST BY 11-21-2024, UPC: 8 13098 02018 4, Lot Code: bak144-6806 due to contamination of Listeria monocytogenes.  Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young chil</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 18:49:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/baker-farms-recalls-baker-brand-curly-mustard-due-listeria-monocytogenes-contamination</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Russ Davis Wholesale Recalls Multiple Products Due to Potential Salmonella Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/russ-davis-wholesale-recalls-multiple-products-due-potential-salmonella-risk</link>
  <description>Russ Davis Wholesale of Wadena, MN, is recalling multiple products out of an abundance of caution because they contain recalled cucumbers from Baloian Farms which have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young childr</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 11:40:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/russ-davis-wholesale-recalls-multiple-products-due-potential-salmonella-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Baloian Farms of Arizona Co., Recalls Whole Fresh American Cucumbers Because of Possible Health Risks Due to Salmonella</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/baloian-farms-arizona-co-recalls-whole-fresh-american-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risks-due</link>
  <description>Baloian Farms of Arizona Co., Inc. (Baloian) is recalling all sizes of whole fresh American cucumbers packaged in bulk cardboard containers labeled with the “Pamela” brand, a generic white box with a sticker that provides the implicated grower’s name, “Agrotato, S.A. de C.V.,” or a clear PamPak bran</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 23:05:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/baloian-farms-arizona-co-recalls-whole-fresh-american-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risks-due</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Gracie’s Kitchen’s Inc. Recalls Read-To-Eat Products Manufactured Between 11/4 and 11/13/24 Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/gracies-kitchens-inc-recalls-read-eat-products-manufactured-between-114-and-111324-because-possible</link>
  <description>Gracie’s Kitchens of New Haven, CT is recalling all ready-to-eat fruit and vegetable products manufactured at the facility from 11/4-11/13/24, because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young c</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:50:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/gracies-kitchens-inc-recalls-read-eat-products-manufactured-between-114-and-111324-because-possible</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Handsome Brook Farms Issues Recall of Kirkland Signature Organic Pasture Raised 24-Count Eggs Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/handsome-brook-farms-issues-recall-kirkland-signature-organic-pasture-raised-24-count-eggs-because</link>
  <description>Handsome Brook Farms is voluntarily recalling 10,800 retail units of the Organic Pasture Raised 24-Count Eggs sold under the Kirkland Signature brand name because these eggs have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:15:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/handsome-brook-farms-issues-recall-kirkland-signature-organic-pasture-raised-24-count-eggs-because</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sunfed Produce, LLC Recalls Whole Fresh American Cucumbers Because of Possible Health Risks Due to Salmonella </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sunfed-produce-llc-recalls-whole-fresh-american-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risks-due</link>
  <description>SunFed Produce, LLC (SunFed) is recalling all sizes of whole fresh American cucumbers packaged in bulk cardboard containers labeled with the “SunFed” label or in a generic white box or black plastic crate with a sticker that provides the implicated grower’s name, “Agrotato, S.A. de C.V.,” (photos b</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:31:00 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sunfed-produce-llc-recalls-whole-fresh-american-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risks-due</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
