<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.fda.gov/">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA Food Safety Recalls RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://www.fda.gov/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Jody’s Inc. Recalls Cabot Creamery Sea Salt Caramel Cheddar Popcorn Due to Undeclared Peanuts</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jodys-inc-recalls-cabot-creamery-sea-salt-caramel-cheddar-popcorn-due-undeclared-peanuts</link>
  <description>Jody’s Inc.  is recalling Cabot Creamery Sea Salt Caramel Cheddar Popcorn 6 oz (170 g) bag, lot number 2519907B1, Best If Enjoyed By: 07 15 26 UPC 8 50016 95530 6, due to presence of undeclared peanuts. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to peanuts run the risk of serious or life-threa</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:53:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jodys-inc-recalls-cabot-creamery-sea-salt-caramel-cheddar-popcorn-due-undeclared-peanuts</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Haitai, Inc. Recalls Haetae (HT) Brand Cinnamon Powder 8 oz of Possible Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/haitai-inc-recalls-haetae-ht-brand-cinnamon-powder-8-oz-possible-risk</link>
  <description>Haitai, Inc of Cerritos, CA (Oct., 15, 2025) is recalling Haetae (HT) brand Cinnamon powder 8 oz because it has the potential to be contaminated with lead. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/haitai-inc-recalls-haetae-ht-brand-cinnamon-powder-8-oz-possible-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Nat’s Nuts Issues Allergy Alert on Potential Undeclared Cashews in Nat’s Nuts Brand Cinnamon Whiskey Pecans</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/nats-nuts-issues-allergy-alert-potential-undeclared-cashews-nats-nuts-brand-cinnamon-whiskey-pecans</link>
  <description>Nat’s Nuts of Rochester, NY is recalling 600 bags of Cinnamon Whiskey Pecans, because they may contain undeclared cashews. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to cashews run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/nats-nuts-issues-allergy-alert-potential-undeclared-cashews-nats-nuts-brand-cinnamon-whiskey-pecans</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Kenz Henz Recalls "Pastured Raised Eggs" Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kenz-henz-recalls-pastured-raised-eggs-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Kenz Henz of Santa Fe, TX, is recalling its 12 count packages of "Grade AA Large Pasture Raised eggs" because they have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with wea</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kenz-henz-recalls-pastured-raised-eggs-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Publix Rich &amp; Creamy Vanilla Ice Cream Voluntarily Recalled in Select Areas</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/publix-rich-creamy-vanilla-ice-cream-voluntarily-recalled-select-areas</link>
  <description>Publix has initiated a voluntary recall on one lot of Publix Rich &amp;amp; Creamy Vanilla Ice Cream, UPC 41415 03043, that may contain an undeclared egg allergen. The product was distributed to stores located in Alabama, Georgia, Kentucky, South Carolina, Tennessee and Florida, except for stores in Jackson</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:18:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/publix-rich-creamy-vanilla-ice-cream-voluntarily-recalled-select-areas</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Raw Bistro Pet Fare Voluntarily Recalls Frozen Beef Entrée Because of Possible Salmonella Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/raw-bistro-pet-fare-voluntarily-recalls-frozen-beef-entree-because-possible-salmonella-health-risk</link>
  <description>October 9, 2025 – Raw Bistro Pet Fare, Cannon Falls, MN is voluntarily recalling two product sizes of its frozen beef dog food because they may be contaminated with Salmonella.  </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:41:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/raw-bistro-pet-fare-voluntarily-recalls-frozen-beef-entree-because-possible-salmonella-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Ben’s Original™ Issues Voluntary Recall of Select Ben's Original Long Grain White, Whole Grain Brown, and Long Grain &amp; Wild Ready Rice Products Due to Possible Presence of Small Stones from Farm</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/bens-originaltm-issues-voluntary-recall-select-bens-original-long-grain-white-whole-grain-brown-and</link>
  <description>Ben's Original is initiating a voluntary recall in the United States on a limited number of Ben's Original Long Grain White, Whole Grain Brown, and Long Grain &amp;amp; Wild Ready Rice products due to the possible presence of small, naturally occurring stones originating from the rice farm. These small ston</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/bens-originaltm-issues-voluntary-recall-select-bens-original-long-grain-white-whole-grain-brown-and</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>CORRECTION: Foodynamics Recalls Raw Dog Barkery, BellePepper Cats, and Kanu Pets Brand Freeze-Dried Pet Treats Because Of Possible Salmonella Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/correction-foodynamics-recalls-raw-dog-barkery-bellepepper-cats-and-kanu-pets-brand-freeze-dried-pet</link>
  <description>Foodynamics is voluntarily recalling specific lots of Raw Dog Barkery,BellePepper Cats, and Kanu Pets brand freeze dried pet treats because they have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella. Salmonella can affect animals eating the products and there is risk to humans handling contaminated</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:07:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/correction-foodynamics-recalls-raw-dog-barkery-bellepepper-cats-and-kanu-pets-brand-freeze-dried-pet</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Tai Foong USA Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Shrimp in Fusia Asian Inspirations Veggie Spring Rolls</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/tai-foong-usa-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-shrimp-fusia-asian-inspirations-veggie-spring-rolls</link>
  <description>Tai Foong USA of Seattle, Washington is recalling a limited quantity of Fusia Asian Inspirations Veggie Spring Rolls, net wt. 10oz, because the product may contain shrimp, a known allergen, that is not declared on the label. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to shrimp or shellfish run</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 17:04:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/tai-foong-usa-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-shrimp-fusia-asian-inspirations-veggie-spring-rolls</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sprouts Farmers Market is Recalling Smoked Mozzarella Pasta Salad  Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sprouts-farmers-market-recalling-smoked-mozzarella-pasta-salad-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>October 8, 2025, Sprouts Farmers Market of Phoenix, AZ is recalling select lots of Smoked Mozzarella Pasta Salad sold from the deli service counter or Grab &amp;amp; Go section because of possible Listeria monocytogenes contamination. Listeria monocytogenes is an organism that can cause serious and sometime</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:33:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sprouts-farmers-market-recalling-smoked-mozzarella-pasta-salad-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Durra Ground Cinnamon 100 G Because of Possible Health Risk  </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/durra-ground-cinnamon-100-g-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Eureka Inc of Pomona, CA (10/6/2025) is recalling Durra Ground Cinnamon 100 gram plastic container because it has the potential to be contaminated with lead. </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:23:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/durra-ground-cinnamon-100-g-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sno Pac Foods Recalls Del Mar 35 LB Bulk Frozen Spinach and 10 oz Organic Frozen Cut  Spinach</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sno-pac-foods-recalls-del-mar-35-lb-bulk-frozen-spinach-and-10-oz-organic-frozen-cut-spinach</link>
  <description>Sno Pac Foods of Caledonia, MN, is recalling Del Mar 35 LB Bulk Organic Frozen Spinach and Sno Pac10 oz Organic Frozen Cut Spinach because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious or sometimes fatal infections in young children, frai</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:59:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sno-pac-foods-recalls-del-mar-35-lb-bulk-frozen-spinach-and-10-oz-organic-frozen-cut-spinach</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Kroger Voluntarily Recalls Two Varieties of Deli Pasta Salads Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kroger-voluntarily-recalls-two-varieties-deli-pasta-salads-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>CINCINNATI, October 4, 2025 – The Kroger Co. (NYSE: KR), said today it has recalled Basil Pesto Bowtie Salad and Smoked Mozzarella Penne Salad that was sold in the Kroger Family of Stores in following states:  AK, AL, AR, AZ, CA, CO, GA, ID, IL, IN, KS, KY, LA, MI, MO, MS, MT, NE, NM, NV, OH, OR, SC</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 13:17:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kroger-voluntarily-recalls-two-varieties-deli-pasta-salads-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Giant Eagle Recalls Smoked Mozzarella Pasta Salad Due to Potential Listeria Monocytogenes Contamination Associated with Nationwide Recall from Nate’s Fine Foods</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/giant-eagle-recalls-smoked-mozzarella-pasta-salad-due-potential-listeria-monocytogenes-contamination</link>
  <description>PITTSBURGH – Giant Eagle, Inc., has issued a voluntary recall of “Smoked Mozzarella Pasta Salad” sold in the prepared foods departments of its Giant Eagle and Market District locations across western Pennsylvania, Ohio, Maryland and Indiana due to potential listeria monocytogenes contamination. This</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:57:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/giant-eagle-recalls-smoked-mozzarella-pasta-salad-due-potential-listeria-monocytogenes-contamination</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Twin Marquis LLC Voluntarily Recalls Twin Marquis® Thick Shanghai Style  Plain Noodle Packages Due to Undeclared Egg </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/twin-marquis-llc-voluntarily-recalls-twin-marquisr-thick-shanghai-style-plain-noodle-packages-due</link>
  <description>BROOKLYN, New York, Oct. 3, 2025 – Twin Marquis LLC is voluntarily recalling one production date of individually wrapped Twin Marquis® Thick Shanghai Style Plain Noodle packages due to possible undeclared egg allergen. The affected packages of Shanghai Style noodles, which do not list egg as an ingr</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:12:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/twin-marquis-llc-voluntarily-recalls-twin-marquisr-thick-shanghai-style-plain-noodle-packages-due</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Best Buy Bones, Inc. Recalls Nature’s Own Pet Chews Bully Bites Because of Possible Salmonella Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/best-buy-bones-inc-recalls-natures-own-pet-chews-bully-bites-because-possible-salmonella-health-risk</link>
  <description>October 3, 2025, Best Buy Bones, Inc. of Mount Morris, Michigan is recalling four lots of Nature’s Own Pet Chews Bully Bites 1 Pound pet treats in 16 oz. bags with a shared expiration date of September 2027because it has the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella. Salmonella can affect animals</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:28:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/best-buy-bones-inc-recalls-natures-own-pet-chews-bully-bites-because-possible-salmonella-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Doan’s Bakery Issues Allergy Update on Undeclared Wheat and Milk Allergens in Bundt Cakes</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/doans-bakery-issues-allergy-update-undeclared-wheat-and-milk-allergens-bundt-cakes</link>
  <description>Doan’s Bakery of Woodland Hills, CA is recalling White Chocolate Coconut and Carrot Bundt Cakes because they may contain undeclared wheat and milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to wheat and/or milk run the risk of experiencing a serious or life-threatening reaction if they consum</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:49:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/doans-bakery-issues-allergy-update-undeclared-wheat-and-milk-allergens-bundt-cakes</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>UPDATE - Albertsons Companies Voluntarily Recalls Select Store-Made Deli Items Containing  Bowtie Pasta Supplied by Fresh Creative Foods Due to an Ingredient Recall for Possible Listeria monocytogenes Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/update-albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-select-store-made-deli-items-containing-bowtie-pasta</link>
  <description>Following a recall initiated by Fresh Creative Foods, a division of Reser’s Fine Foods, Inc., Albertsons Companies has voluntarily recalled select store-made deli items, supplied by Fresh Creative Foods, due to possible Listeria monocytogenes contamination. The recall was initiated because these pro</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:17:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/update-albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-select-store-made-deli-items-containing-bowtie-pasta</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Demers Food Group Voluntarily Recalls Select Scott &amp; Jon's Shrimp Scampi with Linguini  Bowls Due to an Ingredient Recall Initiated by Nate’s Fine Foods for Possible Listeria  Monocytogenes Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/demers-food-group-voluntarily-recalls-select-scott-jons-shrimp-scampi-linguini-bowls-due-ingredient</link>
  <description>Following a recall initiated by Nate’s Fine Foods of Roseville, CA, Demers Food Group has voluntarily recalled select Scott &amp;amp; Jon's Shrimp Scampi with Linguini due to possible Listeria monocytogenes contamination. The voluntary recall was initiated because these products contain a recalled linguini </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:28:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/demers-food-group-voluntarily-recalls-select-scott-jons-shrimp-scampi-linguini-bowls-due-ingredient</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Abdallah Candies Issues a Voluntary Recall of Pecan Caramel Clusters Due to Undeclared, Mislabeled Allergens</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/abdallah-candies-issues-voluntary-recall-pecan-caramel-clusters-due-undeclared-mislabeled-allergens</link>
  <description>Abdallah Candies is voluntarily recalling a specific lot of Pecan Caramel Clusters, due to a mislabeled allergen.  Product contains Cashews that were not listed on the product label.  Product was sold and distributed exclusively to Lunds &amp;amp; Byerlys, as a private label, sold in the state of Minnesota.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:34:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/abdallah-candies-issues-voluntary-recall-pecan-caramel-clusters-due-undeclared-mislabeled-allergens</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
