<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.fda.gov/">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA Food Safety Recalls RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://www.fda.gov/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Best Buy Bones, Inc. Recalls Nature’s Own Pet Chews Bully Bites Because of Possible Salmonella Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/best-buy-bones-inc-recalls-natures-own-pet-chews-bully-bites-because-possible-salmonella-health-risk</link>
  <description>October 3, 2025, Best Buy Bones, Inc. of Mount Morris, Michigan is recalling four lots of Nature’s Own Pet Chews Bully Bites 1 Pound pet treats in 16 oz. bags with a shared expiration date of September 2027because it has the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella. Salmonella can affect animals</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:28:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/best-buy-bones-inc-recalls-natures-own-pet-chews-bully-bites-because-possible-salmonella-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Doan’s Bakery Issues Allergy Update on Undeclared Wheat and Milk Allergens in Bundt Cakes</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/doans-bakery-issues-allergy-update-undeclared-wheat-and-milk-allergens-bundt-cakes</link>
  <description>Doan’s Bakery of Woodland Hills, CA is recalling White Chocolate Coconut and Carrot Bundt Cakes because they may contain undeclared wheat and milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to wheat and/or milk run the risk of experiencing a serious or life-threatening reaction if they consum</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:49:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/doans-bakery-issues-allergy-update-undeclared-wheat-and-milk-allergens-bundt-cakes</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>UPDATE - Albertsons Companies Voluntarily Recalls Select Store-Made Deli Items Containing  Bowtie Pasta Supplied by Fresh Creative Foods Due to an Ingredient Recall for Possible Listeria monocytogenes Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/update-albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-select-store-made-deli-items-containing-bowtie-pasta</link>
  <description>Following a recall initiated by Fresh Creative Foods, a division of Reser’s Fine Foods, Inc., Albertsons Companies has voluntarily recalled select store-made deli items, supplied by Fresh Creative Foods, due to possible Listeria monocytogenes contamination. The recall was initiated because these pro</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:17:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/update-albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-select-store-made-deli-items-containing-bowtie-pasta</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Demers Food Group Voluntarily Recalls Select Scott &amp; Jon's Shrimp Scampi with Linguini  Bowls Due to an Ingredient Recall Initiated by Nate’s Fine Foods for Possible Listeria  Monocytogenes Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/demers-food-group-voluntarily-recalls-select-scott-jons-shrimp-scampi-linguini-bowls-due-ingredient</link>
  <description>Following a recall initiated by Nate’s Fine Foods of Roseville, CA, Demers Food Group has voluntarily recalled select Scott &amp;amp; Jon's Shrimp Scampi with Linguini due to possible Listeria monocytogenes contamination. The voluntary recall was initiated because these products contain a recalled linguini </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:28:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/demers-food-group-voluntarily-recalls-select-scott-jons-shrimp-scampi-linguini-bowls-due-ingredient</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Abdallah Candies Issues a Voluntary Recall of Pecan Caramel Clusters Due to Undeclared, Mislabeled Allergens</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/abdallah-candies-issues-voluntary-recall-pecan-caramel-clusters-due-undeclared-mislabeled-allergens</link>
  <description>Abdallah Candies is voluntarily recalling a specific lot of Pecan Caramel Clusters, due to a mislabeled allergen.  Product contains Cashews that were not listed on the product label.  Product was sold and distributed exclusively to Lunds &amp;amp; Byerlys, as a private label, sold in the state of Minnesota.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:34:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/abdallah-candies-issues-voluntary-recall-pecan-caramel-clusters-due-undeclared-mislabeled-allergens</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sea Port Products Corp is Recalling Raw Frozen Easy Peel White Shrimp Because Product May Have Become Contaminated with Cesium-137 (Cs-137)</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sea-port-products-corp-recalling-raw-frozen-easy-peel-white-shrimp-because-product-may-have-become</link>
  <description>Sea Port Products Corp of Kirkland, WA is voluntarily recalling a limited amount of Sea Port brand bagged Frozen Raw Easy Peel White Shrimp Jumbo size 16/20 count/lb because they may have been prepared, packed, or held under insanitary conditions whereby they may have become contaminated with Cesium</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:08:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sea-port-products-corp-recalling-raw-frozen-easy-peel-white-shrimp-because-product-may-have-become</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Wholesale Produce Supply of Minneapolis, Minnesota is Recalling Fresh Cut/Processed Cantaloupe, Because it has the Potential to be Contaminated With Listeria Monocytogenes</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/wholesale-produce-supply-minneapolis-minnesota-recalling-fresh-cutprocessed-cantaloupe-because-it</link>
  <description>Wholesale Produce Supply of Minneapolis, Minnesota is Recalling Fresh Cut/Processed Cantaloupe, Because it has the Potential to be Contaminated With Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:07:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/wholesale-produce-supply-minneapolis-minnesota-recalling-fresh-cutprocessed-cantaloupe-because-it</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Albertsons Companies Voluntarily Recalls Select Store-Made Deli Items Containing  Bowtie Pasta Supplied by Fresh Creative Foods Due to an Ingredient Recall for Possible Listeria monocytogenes Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-select-store-made-deli-items-containing-bowtie-pasta</link>
  <description>Following a recall initiated by Fresh Creative Foods, a division of Reser’s Fine Foods, Inc., Albertsons Companies has voluntarily recalled five store-made deli items, supplied by Fresh Creative Foods, due to possible Listeria monocytogenes contamination. The recall was initiated because these produ</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:24:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-select-store-made-deli-items-containing-bowtie-pasta</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>New Age International Recalls Signature Enoki Mushrooms Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-age-international-recalls-signature-enoki-mushrooms-due-potential-health-risk</link>
  <description>New Age International Inc of Brooklyn, NY 11206 is recalling its 200g (7.05OZ) packaged of Signature Enoki Mushroom, Product of K Food (Korea Food Signature) because they may be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young chil</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:52:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-age-international-recalls-signature-enoki-mushrooms-due-potential-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>SLR Food Distribution, Inc. Recalls Wise Wife Brand Ground Cinnamon Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/slr-food-distribution-inc-recalls-wise-wife-brand-ground-cinnamon-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>SLR Food Distribution of Hicksville, NY is recalling Wise Wife brand Cinnamon, because it has the potential to be contaminated with elevated levels of lead. Short term exposures to very low levels of lead may not elicit any symptoms.  It is possible that increased blood lead levels may be the only </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:21:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/slr-food-distribution-inc-recalls-wise-wife-brand-ground-cinnamon-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Georgia Nut Company (GNC), Third-Party Manufacturer for Tru Fru, LLC Issues Voluntary Recall of  Specific Varieties of Tru Fru Freeze Dried Products Due to Potential Presence of Metal in Product</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/georgia-nut-company-gnc-third-party-manufacturer-tru-fru-llc-issues-voluntary-recall-specific</link>
  <description>Today, Tru Fru, LLC announced that its third-party manufacturer, Georgia Nut Company (GNC) issued a voluntary recall of specific varieties of Tru Fru Freeze Dried products due to the potential presence of metal in the product. Hard or sharp foreign objects in food may cause traumatic injury includi</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:54:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/georgia-nut-company-gnc-third-party-manufacturer-tru-fru-llc-issues-voluntary-recall-specific</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Gansu Zhaofeng Agricultural Development Co., Ltd. Is Voluntarily Recalling Its Dried Bean Curd Due to Undeclared Wheat</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/gansu-zhaofeng-agricultural-development-co-ltd-voluntarily-recalling-its-dried-bean-curd-due</link>
  <description>Gansu Zhaofeng Agricultural Development Co., Ltd.in Hui County Industrial Concentration Zone, Longnan City, Gansu Province has voluntarily recalled 500g/bag G&amp;amp;L FOOD Dried Bean Curd for failing to declare the allergen wheat. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to wheat run the risk of s</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/gansu-zhaofeng-agricultural-development-co-ltd-voluntarily-recalling-its-dried-bean-curd-due</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Lawrence Wholesale LLC Recalls Kroger Bagged Frozen Shrimp and Kroger Frozen Shrimp Products Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/lawrence-wholesale-llc-recalls-kroger-bagged-frozen-shrimp-and-kroger-frozen-shrimp-products-because</link>
  <description>Lawrence Wholesale LLC of Vernon, CA is recalling a limited quantity of Kroger bagged frozen shrimp and Kroger frozen shrimp products because they may have been prepared, packed, or held under insanitary conditions whereby they may have become contaminated with Cesium-137 (Cs-137). </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 21:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/lawrence-wholesale-llc-recalls-kroger-bagged-frozen-shrimp-and-kroger-frozen-shrimp-products-because</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Updated Release: Southwind Foods, LLC Recalls Frozen Shrimp Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/updated-release-southwind-foods-llc-recalls-frozen-shrimp-because-possible-health-risk-0</link>
  <description>Southwind Foods, LLC of Carson, California is voluntarily recalling a limited quantity of Frozen Shrimp, due to possible radionuclide (Cesium-137) contamination. Cs-137 is a manmade radioisotope of cesium. Traces of Cs-137 are widespread and can be present in the environment at background levels, an</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 18:23:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/updated-release-southwind-foods-llc-recalls-frozen-shrimp-because-possible-health-risk-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>AquaStar (USA) Corp Recalls AquaStar Raw Shrimp Skewers Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/aquastar-usa-corp-recalls-aquastar-raw-shrimp-skewers-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>September 23, 2025, AquaStar (USA) Corp of Seattle, WA is recalling approximately 8,000 bags (net wt. 1.25lbs) of AquaStar Raw Peeled Tail-on Shrimp Skewers (see photo), imported from Indonesia, because they may have been prepared, packed, or held under insanitary conditions whereby they may have be</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:48:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/aquastar-usa-corp-recalls-aquastar-raw-shrimp-skewers-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sprout Organics Expands Voluntary Recall of Sweet Potato Apple and Spinach to Include Additional Lot Codes</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sprout-organics-expands-voluntary-recall-sweet-potato-apple-and-spinach-include-additional-lot-codes</link>
  <description>Sprout Organics is expanding its September 16, 2025 recall of Sprout Organics® Sweet Potato Apple and Spinach, due to potentially elevated lead levels, to include additional lots.   </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sprout-organics-expands-voluntary-recall-sweet-potato-apple-and-spinach-include-additional-lot-codes</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Western United Fish Company Recalls Kirkland Signature Brand Ahi Tuna Wasabi Poke Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/western-united-fish-company-recalls-kirkland-signature-brand-ahi-tuna-wasabi-poke-because-possible</link>
  <description>September 20, 2025, Western United Fish Company dba Annasea Foods Group of Kent, WA is recalling 3,314.7 lbs. of Kirkland Signature brand Ahi Tuna Wasabi Poke, Costco Item Number of 17193, with the Sell By Date of 9/22/2025, because the green onions used in the product have the potential to be cont</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:54:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/western-united-fish-company-recalls-kirkland-signature-brand-ahi-tuna-wasabi-poke-because-possible</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Aquastar (USA) Corp Recalls Kroger Frozen Raw EZ Peel, Kroger Mercado Frozen Cooked Shrimp, and Aquastar Raw Shrimp Skewers Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/aquastar-usa-corp-recalls-kroger-frozen-raw-ez-peel-kroger-mercado-frozen-cooked-shrimp-and-aquastar</link>
  <description>September 19, 2025, AquaStar (USA) Corp of Seattle, WA is recalling:  approximately 49,920 bags (net wt. 2lbs) of Kroger Raw Colossal EZ Peel Shrimp approximately 18,000 bags (net wt. 2lbs) of Kroger Mercado Cooked Medium Peeled Tail-Off Shrimp approximately 17,264 bags (net wt. 1.25lbs) of AquaSt</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 13:24:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/aquastar-usa-corp-recalls-kroger-frozen-raw-ez-peel-kroger-mercado-frozen-cooked-shrimp-and-aquastar</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Goot Essa Recalls Der Mutterschaf Cheese Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/goot-essa-recalls-der-mutterschaf-cheese-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Goot Essa LLC of Howard, PA is recalling one lot totaling 64 pounds, batch 33, of its Goot Essa brand Der Mutterschaf Cheese because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail a</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:18:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/goot-essa-recalls-der-mutterschaf-cheese-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sprout Organics Voluntarily Recalls One Lot of Sweet Potato Apple and Spinach Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sprout-organics-voluntarily-recalls-one-lot-sweet-potato-apple-and-spinach-due-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Sprout Organics has initiated a voluntary recall of one lot of Sprout Organics® Sweet Potato Apple and Spinach because it may contain elevated levels of lead. </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:26:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sprout-organics-voluntarily-recalls-one-lot-sweet-potato-apple-and-spinach-due-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
