<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.fda.gov/">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA Food Safety Recalls RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://www.fda.gov/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Hofood99 Inc Recalls Enoki Mushroom Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/hofood99-inc-recalls-enoki-mushroom-due-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Hofood99 Inc of Brooklyn, NY 11231 is recalling its 200g packages of Enoki Mushroom, because they may be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/hofood99-inc-recalls-enoki-mushroom-due-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Bornstein Seafoods Inc Recalls Cooked &amp; Peeled Ready-To-Eat Coldwater Shrimp Meat Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/bornstein-seafoods-inc-recalls-cooked-peeled-ready-eat-coldwater-shrimp-meat-because-possible-health</link>
  <description>June 10, 2025, Bornstein Seafoods of Bellingham, Washington is recalling 44,550 Lbs. of Cooked &amp;amp; Peeled Ready-To-Eat Coldwater Shrimp Meat (see table below for multiple lot codes) because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and som</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:32:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/bornstein-seafoods-inc-recalls-cooked-peeled-ready-eat-coldwater-shrimp-meat-because-possible-health</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>P. East Trading Corp Distributors Issues Alert on Uneviscerated 'Salted Smoked Split Herring’ Due to Potential Clostridium Botulinum Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/p-east-trading-corp-distributors-issues-alert-uneviscerated-salted-smoked-split-herring-due</link>
  <description>P. East Trading Corp. of Bronx, NY is recalling Salted Smoked Split Herring because the product was found to be over 5" in length and uneviscerated, as such having potential to be contaminated with Clostridium botulinum, a bacterium which can cause life-threatening illness or death. Consumer</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:12:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/p-east-trading-corp-distributors-issues-alert-uneviscerated-salted-smoked-split-herring-due</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>August Egg Company Recalls Shell Eggs Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/august-egg-company-recalls-shell-eggs-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>August Egg Company of Hilmar, CA is recalling 1,700,000 dozen brown cage free and brown certified organic eggs, because they have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and other</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/august-egg-company-recalls-shell-eggs-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Firehook of Virginia Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Sesame in Classic Sea Salt Crackers</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/firehook-virginia-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-sesame-classic-sea-salt-crackers</link>
  <description>Firehook of Virginia is recalling one lot of Firehook brand Classic Sea Salt Organic Crackers because they may contain undeclared sesame. </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/firehook-virginia-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-sesame-classic-sea-salt-crackers</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Tgd Cuts, LLC Initiated Voluntary Recall of Cucumber from Bedner Growers Inc., Which Had the Potential to Be Contaminated with Salmonella</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/tgd-cuts-llc-initiated-voluntary-recall-cucumber-bedner-growers-inc-which-had-potential-be</link>
  <description>TGD Cuts, LLC of Jessup, MD has initiated a voluntary recall of the specific tub and tray items listed below because they contained cucumber from Bedner Growers Inc., which had the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/tgd-cuts-llc-initiated-voluntary-recall-cucumber-bedner-growers-inc-which-had-potential-be</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Camerican International, Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Aldi Brand Casa Mamita Churro Bites Filled with Chocolate Hazelnut Cream </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/camerican-international-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-aldi-brand-casa-mamita-churro-bites</link>
  <description>Camerican International of Paramus, NJ is recalling 7.05 oz boxes of Aldi Brand Casa Mamita Churro Bites Filled with Chocolate Hazelnut Cream because they may contain undeclared milk.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic react</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:05:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/camerican-international-inc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-aldi-brand-casa-mamita-churro-bites</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Homegrown Family Foods Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Shore Lunch Oven Style Breader &amp; Batter Mix</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/homegrown-family-foods-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-shore-lunch-oven-style-breader-batter</link>
  <description>Homegrown Family Foods is recalling its Shore Lunch Oven Style Breader &amp;amp; Batter Mix 6oz Box due to the presence of undeclared milk. Individuals with an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk risk serious or life-threatening allergic reactions if they consume this product. For ease of identification, </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/homegrown-family-foods-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-shore-lunch-oven-style-breader-batter</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Isabelle’s Kitchen Inc. Recalls Refrigerated Deli Salads Containing Fresh Cucumbers Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/isabelles-kitchen-inc-recalls-refrigerated-deli-salads-containing-fresh-cucumbers-because-possible</link>
  <description>Isabelle's Kitchen, Inc., Harleysville, PA, is recalling 946 cases of refrigerated deli salads containing fresh cucumbers recalled by Bedner Grower’s, Inc. because they have potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young chil</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:07:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/isabelles-kitchen-inc-recalls-refrigerated-deli-salads-containing-fresh-cucumbers-because-possible</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Supreme Service Solutions LLC Voluntarily Recalls Supreme Vegetable Products Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/supreme-service-solutions-llc-voluntarily-recalls-supreme-vegetable-products-because-possible-health-0</link>
  <description>Supreme Service Solutions LLC. (dba Supreme Produce) is voluntarily recalling items purchased from Bedner Growers Inc. (purchased from Kroger and its affiliates ) due to possible contamination with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frai</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 16:22:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/supreme-service-solutions-llc-voluntarily-recalls-supreme-vegetable-products-because-possible-health-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Santa Monica Seafood Voluntarily Recalls Atlantic Salmon Portions with Seafood Stuffing Due to Undeclared Soy </title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/santa-monica-seafood-voluntarily-recalls-atlantic-salmon-portions-seafood-stuffing-due-undeclared</link>
  <description>May 24, 2025, Santa Monica Seafood of Rancho Dominguez, CA, is voluntarily recalling Atlantic Salmon Portions with Seafood Stuffing because it may contain undeclared soy. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to soy risk a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 16:56:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/santa-monica-seafood-voluntarily-recalls-atlantic-salmon-portions-seafood-stuffing-due-undeclared</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Spectrum Brands Pet LLC Recalls a Single Lot of Tetra Reptomin Reptile Food for Aquatic Turtles Because of Possible Salmonella Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/spectrum-brands-pet-llc-recalls-single-lot-tetra-reptomin-reptile-food-aquatic-turtles-because</link>
  <description>Spectrum Brands Pet LLC (“SPG”) is voluntarily recalling its Tetra ReptoMin 3-In-1 SELECT-A-FOOD reptile food product intended for aquatic turtles due to potential contamination with Salmonella. The product is packaged in a plastic, 1.56oz container with a green label and a UPC Bar Code #: 0 46798 7</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:01:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/spectrum-brands-pet-llc-recalls-single-lot-tetra-reptomin-reptile-food-aquatic-turtles-because</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>JFE Franchising, Inc. Recalls A Limited Number of Cucumber Products   Because Of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jfe-franchising-inc-recalls-limited-number-cucumber-products-because-possible-health-risk-0</link>
  <description>Houston, TX (May 23, 2025) - JFE Franchising, Inc. of Houston, TX, is recalling a limited number of fresh-cut cucumber items and sushi products containing cucumber because they may be contaminated with Salmonella.  </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:40:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/jfe-franchising-inc-recalls-limited-number-cucumber-products-because-possible-health-risk-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Big Y Foods Recalls Made-To-Order Subs, Wraps and Paninis Sold in Massachusetts and Connecticut Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/big-y-foods-recalls-made-order-subs-wraps-and-paninis-sold-massachusetts-and-connecticut-because</link>
  <description>Big Y Foods of Springfield, MA is voluntarily recalling some Made-To-Order Subs, Wraps and Paninis sold between 5/20 and 5/21 in some Massachusetts and Connecticut retail stores (listed below), because they have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious a</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:10:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/big-y-foods-recalls-made-order-subs-wraps-and-paninis-sold-massachusetts-and-connecticut-because</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Albertsons Companies Voluntarily Recalls Three Store-Made Deli Items  Containing Recalled Cucumber Supplied by Fresh Creative Foods Due to Possible Salmonella Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-three-store-made-deli-items-containing-recalled-cucumber</link>
  <description>Following a recall initiated by Fresh Creative Foods, a division of Reser’s Fine Foods, Inc., Albertsons Companies has voluntarily recalled three store-made deli items, supplied by Fresh Creative Foods, due to possible Salmonella contamination and in association with an active illness outbreak. The </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:05:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/albertsons-companies-voluntarily-recalls-three-store-made-deli-items-containing-recalled-cucumber</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>The Coastal Companies Issues Voluntary Recall on Items with Fresh Start Cucumbers Due to the Potential for Salmonella Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/coastal-companies-issues-voluntary-recall-items-fresh-start-cucumbers-due-potential-salmonella</link>
  <description>The Coastal Companies is issuing a voluntary recall of 17 products that were produced from cucumbers grown by Bedner Growers, Inc. and distributed by Fresh Start Produce Sales, Inc. due to the potential for Salmonella contamination. These products were distributed by East Coast Fresh in Laurel, MD a</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:18:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/coastal-companies-issues-voluntary-recall-items-fresh-start-cucumbers-due-potential-salmonella</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Walmart Inc. Recalls Marketside Fresh Cut Cucumber Slices in Select Texas Stores Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/walmart-inc-recalls-marketside-fresh-cut-cucumber-slices-select-texas-stores-because-possible-health</link>
  <description>BENTONVILLE, Ark. May 22nd, 2025 Walmart Inc. is voluntarily recalling Marketside Fresh Cut Cucumber Slices, produced in select stores located in Texas, because of the potential for Salmonella contamination. The recall was initiated because this product may contain recalled whole cucumbers supplie</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/walmart-inc-recalls-marketside-fresh-cut-cucumber-slices-select-texas-stores-because-possible-health</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Ukrop’s Homestyle Foods Announces Recall Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ukrops-homestyle-foods-announces-recall-due-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Ukrop’s Homestyle Foods, LLC, Richmond, VA announced today that it is recalling three of its products in reaction to the Bedner Growers’ recall of cucumbers due to its potential to be contaminated with Salmonella.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:26:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ukrops-homestyle-foods-announces-recall-due-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>PennRose Farms Issues Recall of Whole Cucumbers  Because Of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/pennrose-farms-issues-recall-whole-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Wellington, FL (May 21, 2025)—PennRose Farms, LLC is recalling 5-pound mesh bags of whole cucumbers because they have the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weake</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:55:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/pennrose-farms-issues-recall-whole-cucumbers-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>New Grains Gluten Free Bakery Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Eggs, Tree Nuts, Soy, and Milk in Bakery Products</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-grains-gluten-free-bakery-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-eggs-tree-nuts-soy-and-milk-bakery</link>
  <description>May 21, 2025 — Spanish Fork, Utah — New Grains Gluten Free Bakery is recalling a variety of products, including breads, bagels, cookies, and croutons, because they may contain undeclared eggs, tree nuts, soy, and milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs, tree nuts, soy, or milk</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:12:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/new-grains-gluten-free-bakery-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-eggs-tree-nuts-soy-and-milk-bakery</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
